Guide to the United States Information Agency Broadcast Service Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
United States Information Agency Broadcast Service Records,
1954-1956
United States Information Agency. Broadcast Service Munich Radio Center.
ca. 950 items (19 boxes).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library. Bakhmeteff Archive New York, NY.
4078210
History
Scope and Content
Mimeographed daily broadcast content reports of the U.S. Information Agency, Broadcast Service, Munich Radio Center, the "Voice of America." The reports are from the end of November 1954 through May 1956.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 1 series:
Series I: Daily Broadcast Content Report
Subjects
Voice of America (Radio program)
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
11/--/81 Reports
- Series I: Daily Broadcast Content Report
  - Subseries I.1: Munich Radio Center, the "Voice of America"
    - November 1954 (Box 1)
    - December 1954 (Box 2)
    - January 1955 (Box 3)
    - February 1955 (Box 4)
    - March 1955 (Box 5)
    - April 1955 (Box 6)
    - May 1955 (Box 7)
    - June 1955 (Box 8)
    - July 1955 (Box 9)
    - August 1955 (Box 10)
    - September 1955 (Box 11)
    - October 1955 (Box 12)
    - November 1955 (Box 13)
    - December 1955 (Box 14)
    - January 1956 (Box 15)
    - February 1956 (Box 16)
    - March 1956 (Box 17)
    - April 1956 (Box 18)
    - May 1956 (Box 19)